
const questionData = [{
    Question: "1. Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    Options: [{ option: "Virtual DOM" },
    { option: "Original DOM" },
    { option: "Both A and B" },
    { option: "None of the above" }],
    Correct_Answer: "1",
    Flag: "1"
  },
  {
    Question: "2. What is ReactJS?",
    Options: [{ option: "Server-side framework" },
    { option: "user interface framework" },
    { option: "both a and b" },
    { option: "none of the above" }],
    Correct_Answer: "2",
    Flag: "2"
  },
  {
    Question: "3. Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
    Options: [{ option: "Render with arguments" },
    { option: "setState" },
    { option: "PropsTypes" },
    { option: "props" }],
    Correct_Answer: "4",
    Flag: "3"
  },
  {
    Question: "4. Who created React.js?",
    Options: [{ option: "Jordan Mike" },
    { option: "Jordan Walke" },
    { option: "Tim Lee" },
    { option: "Jordan Lee" }],
    Correct_Answer: "2",
    Flag: "4"
  },
  {
    Question: "5. In which language is React.js written?",
    Options: [{ option: "Python" },
    { option: "JavaScript" },
    { option: "Java" },
    { option: "PHP" }],
    Correct_Answer: "2",
    Flag: "5"
  },
  {
    Question: "6. What is Babel?",
    Options: [{ option: "JavaScript compiler" },
    { option: "JavaScript interpreter" },
    { option: "JavaScript transpiler" },
    { option: "none of the above" }],
    Correct_Answer: "1",
    Flag: "6"
  },
  {
    Question: "7. Identify the command used to create a react app.",
    Options: [
      { option: "npm install create-react-app" },
    { option: "npm install -g create-react-app" },
    { option: "install -g create-react-app" },
    { option: "none of the above" }],
    Correct_Answer: "2",
    Flag: "7"
  },
  {
    Question: "8. Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
    Options: [{ option: "3000" },
    { option: "3306" },
    { option: "3030" },
    { option: "8080" }],
    Correct_Answer: "4",
    Flag: "8"
  },
  {
    Question: "9. How many elements can a valid react component return?",
    Options: [{ option: "1" },
    { option: "2" },
    { option: "3" },
    { option: "4" }],
    Correct_Answer: "1",
    Flag: "9"
  },
  {
    Question: "10. A state in React.js is also known as?",
    Options: [{ option: "The internal storage of the component" },
    { option: "External storage of the component" },
    { option: "Permanent storage" },
    { option: "All of the above" }],
    Correct_Answer: "1",
    Flag: "10"
  },
  ];
  export default questionData